# MOHAMED HAMED

#### **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

muhmdhamed757@gmail.com

+201029288339

https://github.com/mohamid97?tab=repositories

### **Summary**

I am a full stack developer with a solid background in PHP, Laravel, and knowledge in various front-end and backend languages, responsive frameworks, and databases. I have experience working on large-scale projects such as e-commerce websites and ERP systems.

## **Experience**

Mishkat Nour Foundation - Full stack developer - January 2023 - current

- Developed human resource and accounting systems using Laravel and Vue.js.
- Implemented new features and enhanced performance.
- Created reliable, secure, and scalable APIs.

PeoFree Company - Backend developer - Septemper 2022 - December 2022

- Worked on E-commerce projects using the Laravel framework.
- Developed web-based applications from scratch.

### **Projects**

**Bneksy** - https://bneksy.com - Laravel framework

• E-commerce platform for wholesale and retail sales with multi-vendor support and integration with multiple payment methods.

HR System - https://hr.mishkatnour.org - Laravel framework and Vue.js

 Automated calculation of employee benefits and generation of complete company salary and expense sheets.

Accounting System - private - Laravel framework and Vue.js

• Divided into accounting and store management sections for creating accounting constraints, managing stores, suppliers, and invoices.

#### **Education**

Bachelor of computers and information in computer science, faculty of computers and information 2015 - 2019 **Zagaziq university** 

#### **Skills**

#### **Technical Skills**

1- Web design: HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Tailwind

2- Database: Mysql, Redis

3- JavaScript: (ES6, VUE.JS, NUXT.JS, JQUERY)

4- Backend: PHP, Laravel

5- Apis

6- Version control system : Git

7- Knowledge: Wordpress

#### **Soft Skills**

1- Problem solver

2- Work on a team

3- Collaboration